employmentcrossing.com 2010-12-23

# EmploymentCrossing.com - Privacy Policy, Your Privacy is So Important To Us | EmploymentCrossing.com

**PRIVACY**

**EmploymentCrossing will NEVER sell or share ANY of your personal information with ANY third party, ever. All information that our customers provide is held in the utmost care and security and will NEVER be shared with ANY third party.**

**SECURITY**

**The EmploymentCrossing servers use Secure Socket Layer (SSL), an advanced encryption technology that works with Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator (versions 2.0 and higher), Mozilla, Microsoft Internet Explorer (versions 3.0 and higher), and AOL (AOL 3.0 and higher). This encryption provides the best possible protection from unauthorized parties accessing any information you send to us.**

**Effective on: (02/09/2009)**

EmploymentCrossing is committed to protecting the privacy of our users, and we are firmly devoted to maintaining your trust in us. We work extremely hard at safeguarding our customers' important information and keeping it secure. Our privacy policy is designed to help you understand our genuine dedication to preserving your privacy. This Privacy Statement applies to the Site [www.employmentcrossing.com](http://www.employmentcrossing.com/). Confidentiality and discretion are the cornerstones of every job search. We consistently challenge ourselves to rise above every competitor in our honesty and discretion, and we believe we have met this challenge day after day. We have established this Privacy Statement to inform our visitors and users, how we collect, use and store the personal information you submit while using our Site. "Personal Information" applies to information that can be used to identify you, such as your name and email address. 

EmploymentCrossing is a licensee of the TRUSTe privacy program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build trust and confidence in the internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Site [www.employmentcrossing.com](http://www.employmentcrossing.com/). Because EmploymentCrossing wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Statement, you should first contact EmploymentCrossing at [privacy@employmentcrossing.com](mailto:privacy@employmentcrossing.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

**What personally identifiable information is collected on this site?**  
In order to register as an EmploymentCrossing member, users are required to provide pertinent contact information such as their name, an email address, and a mailing address. To complete the sign-up process and subscribe to the service, users are also required to provide financial information, in the form of a valid credit card number and billing address. After subscribing, members may also provide personally identifiable information for other purposes in their use of the site. This includes, but is not limited to, submitting a resume or cover letter. However, any submitted resume or cover letter is viewable only by the person who uploaded or pasted it into the account. Any transmission of these materials can only be achieved through the initiative of the user. EmploymentCrossing does not collect personal information from its subscribers unless they voluntarily and knowingly provide it to us. This means that a user can visit our site without telling us who they are and without revealing any personally identifiable information. The site visitor is never required to provide any personally identifiable information, unless he or she would like to subscribe to the service. 

**Tell a Friend**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, you are asked to provide a friend's name and email address. EmploymentCrossing will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site. EmploymentCrossing does not share this information with any third parties for their promotional purposes. 

**How is the information used?**  
When you supply personal information about yourself for a specific purpose, we use the information for only that purpose (such as to provide the service or information you have requested). Your contact information may also be used to contact you when necessary in order to respond to your inquiries regarding the service. Every communication with EmploymentCrossing is held in strictest confidence and handled with integrity. None of your personal information will be disclosed to a potential employer without you taking affirmative action to disclose this information such as selecting to "apply" for a position within our database. 

Your personal information will not be disclosed to third parties under any circumstances, except as disclosed in this privacy statement. Any general demographic information that we receive will never be utilized to identify you. While it may be used in an aggregated form for research purposes in order to further develop our understanding of the job market or to improve the Web site, none of this demographic information is attributable to your account. This general information may be disseminated or published in its basic form. 

EmploymentCrossing will absolutely never share any information relating to your employment situation or resume with any third parties for their promotional purposes. Each employee of EmploymentCrossing signs a strict confidentiality and nondisclosure agreement to ensure your privacy. 

EmploymentCrossing is one of the [Employment Research Institute](http://www.employmentresearchinstitute.com/) companies, which include Attorney Research Group, BCG Attorney Search, CLE Authority, EdFed, EmploymentCrossing, General Counsel Consulting, Hound.com, JD Journal, JD2B, Judged, Law Firm Staff, Professional Authority, Resume Apple, and Southlake Properties LLC. Each company is a distinct and separately incorporated entity, and each company's databases and servers are maintained independently. The fact that you contacted EmploymentCrossing will not be shared with any other [Employment Research Institute](http://www.employmentresearchinstitute.com/) company or its employees unless you opt-into receiving information from any of these affiliated companies such as when you select to use "Resume Apple" service on our site. By providing your information in the Frame provided noting Resume Apple, you authorize EmploymentCrossing to share your information with Resume Apple to provide the service you're requesting. Each employee of each company signs a strict confidentiality and nondisclosure agreement, ensuring that they do not disclose your private information to any other person or company. 

After contacting EmploymentCrossing, you may be notified of the potentially complementary services of another [Employment Research Institute](http://www.employmentresearchinstitute.com/) company. However, no information regarding your employment status, or information from your resume, will ever be shared with any other [Employment Research Institute](http://www.employmentresearchinstitute.com/) company without your explicit consent. Furthermore, the fact that the offer is coming from another [Employment Research Institute](http://www.employmentresearchinstitute.com/) company will be fully disclosed in the mailing, and you may opt out of such offers at any time as described below. No information will be used for purposes of such offers except your name, email and mailing address and access to such information will be restricted to the sole purpose of communicating with you. 

Should any material changes be made to the manner in which we use personally identifiable information, EmploymentCrossing will post the changes on our Web site no less than 30 days prior to a change. This is done in order to give users time to request removal of their information from our database or to make inquiries about any new practices. 

**Security**  
Personally identifiable information is stored on our database and is not publicly accessible. All EmploymentCrossing employees must sign non-disclosure contracts that ensure the confidentiality of all personally identifiable information before gaining access to such information. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, and meets or exceeds all industry standards for the protection and confidentiality of personally identifiable information. The site uses 128 bit SSL[Secure Socket Layer] encryption to safeguard all financial information. 

**Opt-out**  
If you have registered to receive our newsletter, job updates and/or any other automatically distributed information, you may change this registration status at any time. Simply contact us to have your name removed from the particular distribution list you wish to be removed from. This can be achieved in several ways: 

  * Send an email to: [**opt-out@employmentcrossing.com**](mailto:opt-out@employmentcrossing.com)
  * Send correspondence to the following address:

Consumer Privacy Department  
EmploymentCrossing  
202 S Lake Ave, Unit 250  
Pasadena, CA 91101 

Furthermore, you may opt-out of receiving emails from other [Employment Research Institute](http://www.employmentresearchinstitute.com/) companies at any time by emailing   
[**opt-out@employmentcrossing.com**](mailto:opt-out@employmentcrossing.com). 

**Correct/Update**  
If you would like to verify the data we have received from you or would like to edit any information you have submitted to us, or if you seek to deactivate the use of your personal information, you may contact us directly at the addresses provided above. You also have the option to make any changes to your resume, job settings, and password in the "My Details" section of the EmploymentCrossing main page once you have logged into your account. 

To change your credit card information, please call one of our Customer Service representatives at **626-243-1814**. If your credit card has been lost or has not been granted approval by Verisign, when you attempt to log-in, you will be prompted to sign-up for an account. Simply enter the prior account information along with your new credit card information. All inquiries will receive responses within 30 days of our receipt of them. 

**What anonymous information is collected on this site?**  
IP addresses are briefly logged but discarded within a short period of time. No anonymous information that may be received from visitors is used in any of our work, promotions, or research. These logged files are not connected to a subscriber's personally identifiable information. 

**How does this site use cookies?**  
EmploymentCrossing uses cookies to identify your browser as you visit pages on the EmploymentCrossing Site. The cookies are used to present dynamic content so that you are not presented with identical content on every visit. No information from the cookies is used in any of our work, promotions or research. None of the cookies used by EmploymentCrossing are connected to your personal information. 

We use a third-party tracking service (LinkShare) that uses cookies (log files) to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate (usage, volume statistics and referrals) to monitor the traffic flow and provide targeted service referrals. 

**Links to external pages**  
This site may contain links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website. EmploymentCrossing is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. 

_We Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties in the following ways_ : 

**Service Providers**  
We use a third party, to provide Credit Card Processing for our Site. When you sign up for EmploymentCrossing membership, we share your name, username and billing address to process a charge on your credit card. These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for any other purpose. 

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process such as in complying with a subpoena, judicial proceeding or court order served on EmploymentCrossing. 

In the event of the sale, merger or acquisition of some or all of EmploymentCrossing's assets, your personal information would likely be a part of the transferred assets. We shall notify by email or notice on our Site of your choices in how your information is to be used henceforth. 

**Blog Disclosure**  
If you use a bulletin board, blog, or chat room on this website, you should be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information that you choose to submit in these forums. 

**Testimonials and Live Help**  
Live Chat help is provided in real-time format on EmploymentCrossing. The user is not required to provide any identifying information in order to make use of the Live Chat function. Any information, such as a name or Username, that is shown to the Customer Service representative conducting the Live Chat is provided voluntarily by the user and is discarded when the Chat session expires. Any information that is received in the Live Chat sessions is utilized only for the purpose the user intends it to be used for, and is not saved unless the user requests an action of the Customer Service representative that requires it be saved. We use a third party to host our chat service. We're not responsible for the personally identifiable information a user chooses to disclose while using this chat feature. 

Any testimonials that are provided through the site are published only with a customer's first name and last initial. Testimonials can also be published anonymously, or with only the person's sales field listed. We obtain the consent of our users prior to posting their testimonials on our site. If a user chooses to post personally-identifiable information to our website, it may be used by other users of the website to contact you. We are not responsible for the personally-identifiable information a user chooses to post to our website with their testimonial. 

**For more information**  
If you have any questions, concerns or comments regarding this statement, please email [privacy@employmentcrossing.com](mailto:privacy@employmentcrossing.com).
